Shoppable images in your store help customers see your products in context, engage with their
details, and add them directly to their carts.
If you're using the product highlight or
marquee template, or if you've added a split width section to your page, you can see empty
tiles ready for you.
Click on a tile and find Shoppable Image.
Upload a lifestyle image
showing at least one product, then add the products featured.
You can adjust where
they're active on the image and add more, up to six products.
Click Save.
You can
also add a shoppable Image as the only full width tile in a section.
Add a new
section and your shoppable Image in the same way.